CURRICULUM VITAE

Ashok Dhumak

Mobile:+919623813859 Email:ashokdhum@gmail.com

Objective

To contribute at my best as a experience to serve a reputed organization, which can utilize my skills in the areas of new technological development and also provide a platform for personal growth, while achieving the organizational goals.

Education Qualification					
Course	Institute/College/School	University/Board	Percentage	Year of Passing	
B.E (Electonics And Felecommunication)	Rajendra Mane College Of Engineering And Technology,Maharashtra	Mumbai University	59.23%	2014	
Std XII	Paisa Fund Jr.College Ratnagiri, Mahrashtra.	Kolhapur Board	58%	2009	
Std X	Kamaljabai Mulye Highschool Sangameshwar	Kolhapur Board	75.23%	2007	

Technical Skills & Abilities

Software programming Languages: C, Data Structures, Embedded C, Assembly level language, Python, Microcontrollers Programming, Android Thing, IOT, Basics Of HTML And CSS, Basics RTOS, API.

Linux System Programming: Basic File I/O, Process Management.

Signal Handling, Memory Management, Resource Management, IPC Mechanisms, Mysql Database.

Embedded Boards: Intel 8051, ARM, Raspberry Pi, Arduino Board, NODE MCU.

Microcontrollers Programming: Intel 8051, ARM 32BitSOc's, Arduino IDE.

Tools Chain: GCC, GDB, Make Utility.

Operating Systems: Linux–Ubuntu OS, Windows7/8/10/XP.

Platforms: VI editor, GCC Compiler, Keil uvision.

Communication Standards: I2C, SPI, RS-232, UART, TCP/IP(Socket Programming), MQTT.

Advanced EmbeddedSystemProjects-1

Project Name: LAN Based Data Acquisition System on 8051.

Software used: Keil uVision4.

Language Used: Embedded C, Linux(System Programming), TCPIP(Socket Programming).

Hardware Used: 8051 UC, Alphanumeric Display.

Peripherals Used: ADC,RTC,UART, LDR.

Application:

Collecting Data from Various Sensors and Displaying with Server and Client On Linux Platform.

Academic Project : B.E(Electronics And Telecommunication)

Project Name: Automatic Load Sharing Of Transformer Project Duration: 15August 2014 to 10

May2014

Software used: Keil.

Language Used: C Language

Hardware Work used: 2 Transformers, Current Sensor, Power supply, Microcontroller.

Application:

Our project "Automatic Load Sharing Of Transformer" will work on managing the extra load which is coming from stations. The main idea behind this project is if any extra load occurs on existing transformer then our system will transfer that extra load to another transformer. In this way it will manage that extra load and prevent the damage of transformer which may occure by extra loading.

Work Experience

Company	Duration	Designation	Date
Wipro Infotech	1.5 Years	Desktop Engineer	25 July 2015 To 19 Feb 2017
Vector India Pvt. Ltd.	6 Months	Embedded System Engineer	14 April2017 To 21 Oct 2017
OS3 Infotech Pvt. Ltd.	1 Year	Embedded And IOT Developer	24 November 2017 To 13 November 2018

Personal Traits:

- > Can adjust to different situations and environments.
- > Good team player and possess ability to operate independently.
- ➤ Commitment with work & Hardworking.

Personal Details:		
Name	Ashok T. Dhumak	
Date of Birth	11th Sep,1990	
Language Known	☐ English ☐ Hindi ☐ Marathi	
Interests and Hobbies	Travelling, Playing Cricket.	
Current Address	Rambujharat ki chawl, Narsipada, Hanuman Nagar, Kandivali East- 400101.	
Permanent Address	At-Kurdhunda, Post-Kurdhunda, TQ- Sangameshwar, Dist- Ratnagiri, State- Maharashtra, Pin Code- 415611.	
Mobile No	09623813859	
Marital Status	Unmarried	
E-Mail ID	ashokdhum@gmail.com	

I confirm that the above information is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

Date:

Place: Mumbai.

Ashok Dhumak.